‎MACHI MORI - CUSTOMS OFFICIAL
Amazing! It's like
we stepped inside the painting.
Strong, vivid colors
that envelop the entire body.
-In short, basically, well…
-It's the best, right?
Yes.
It's the best.
That reminds me.
Why did you invite me here?
You told me before
that you were interested in digital art.
That's sweet.
But Mori, don't you ever go
on dates with a boyfriend?
A boyfriend?
A date?
Are you just not interested in romance?
Romance.
Love and affection?
I am interested in it.
You are, huh?
So, what's your type, then?
However, I have yet to define
what romance is.
Who cares about the definition?
Love.
What is it, I wonder.
‎There is major rainfall tonight
‎in Tokyo Prefecture
‎and Kanagawa Prefecture.
‎It is also highly likely
‎there has already been flooding…
Oh man! Oh man!
Hey, you're soaked!
It's a total downpour outside!
The link bridge has a lot of water
flowing through it.
The drainage can't keep up at all.
Dang, it's flooding?
This area was built in a rush after all.
Ah, thank you.
Let's just go home. All flights
must be canceled now, right?
Yes?
Yes.
Flight UNT815 from the Unitia Federation
will be landing shortly.
-What?
-Seriously? In this rain?
-The captain really did their best.
-This is the last flight of the day.
Yes, let's wrap it up smoothly
and go home!
Is love…
a torrential downpour?
You're still thinking about that?
Hurry, let's go.
Yes.
Just this way.
-Two booths, open.
-Please don't rush.
So next in line, please.
-Please be careful.
-Just this way.
-It's okay. Don't worry.
-Next in line, please.
Please watch your step.
This way, please.
-Please watch your step.
-Let's go.
Japanese is fine.
He's third-generation Japanese.
Speaks fluent Japanese too, right?
We're engaged.
We're traveling before our wedding.
I see. Well then, your passports, please.
-Here.
-Thank you.
-I'll just hold it to the glass.
-Be gentle.
-We'll need it later.
-Yes.
-Wonderful.
Leon Araki and Aoi Onodera.
Leon, you are visiting for tourism.
How long is your stay?
Wherever the wind blows,
wherever the stones call.
IMMIGRATION OFFICER, MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
AKIHIKO SEIKE
-Stones?
-He is a gem appraiser.
He travels all around the world.
I run a jewelry company myself,
so we really hit it off.
-We did.
-We did!
And then, I found a gem named Aoi.
Stop it, Leon.
Look, this is the engagement ring
he gave me.
How wonderful.
So, how long is your stay?
-About two weeks, right?
-Ah, yes.
I guess so.
Excuse me. I'll inspect your luggage now.
Yes.
Is that also a form of love?
Pardon?
KEIICHIRO HAYAMI - IMMIGRATION OFFICIAL
-What is this?
-That is a fountain pen.
Adorned with gold and natural gems,
passed down from the former
royal family of the Unitia Federation.
Here you go.
Excuse me, but approximately
how much is it worth?
High-value items
may be subject to taxation.
Oh, well, you cannot put a price tag
on something like this.
That's not what I mean.
-What?
-The interior work is falling behind.
We have less than a year
until the opening, you know?
Miss, please refrain from having
phone calls in the inspection area.
Send me the progress report later.
I've seen her before.
That's Toko Tsuzuki, the entrepreneur.
She's super talented.
She made her mark revitalizing hotels.
You are Ms. Toko Tsuzuki
I plan to get my medical license
in Japan, so…
He is a resident doctor
in the Unitia Federation.
Do you have documents
from your place of study?
Ah, yes.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
-I will inspect your luggage.
-Okay.
All right.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
-Now, please head over there.
-Okay.
Ah, sorry, one at a time.
One more time.
Um…
-What are these?
-Vitamins.
He says they're good
for health and beauty.
Those are only supplements.
Do you have the original container
that shows the ingredients?
I threw it away.
We will need to confirm if these
are permitted entry into the country.
Excuse me.
I also have a few things
I'd like to confirm about Mr. Luca.
Let's step into the secondary room.
The secondary room?
Sorry for the trouble.
Take them to the secondary room.
Okay.
I'll carry your bags.
Excuse me.
I need to get back to the office soon.
Um, please hurry.
Yes, yes, this way.
Hurry! You too, Luca!
What's that?
You found it.
Toko.
I was going to give this
to you in private, but…
Could that be…
-No way, a proposal?
-Right here?
Oh my.
Toko, my love,
you've always been there for me.
Now I want to be there for you.
Will you marry me?
-Whoa!
-What happened?
Please stay calm!
Power will be restored shortly!
Please do not move from where you are!
POWER OUTAGE
EMERGENCY POWER
Toko?
Let go of me!
-What are you doing?
-Stay back!
Don't get any closer.
Fine! Please calm down.
-Come on!
-Everyone, please back away!
-Get back!
-Everyone, get back!
-Let's calm down.
-Get back!
-Gate 24 Inspection Booth,
a man has restrained a female passenger.
Come on. Get back!
Wait…
-Wait…
-Toko!
Hey, hey, hey! Get back.
That's my fountain pen! Excuse me…
-Give that back!
-Stop!
-Get back!
You little…
Hayami!
No one come in!
Next time, I'll really stab someone!
-Are you okay?
-Thank you.
You're a doctor, right?
-Could you examine him?
-Sure.
Don't move!
I don't trust you.
Gunji.
How did you find me here?
D-Do you know each other?
He's a former coworker.
Ex-boyfriend.
Right?
I came here to protect you.
Because
I still love you.
Is this also…
love?
The meeting just ended.
The airport director is here too.
Please tell me the situation.
The man is Ryosuke Gunji.
Using a fountain pen, he has taken
two passengers and two staff hostage
and barricaded himself in.
Passengers are being held hostage.
What about the other passengers?
We evacuated them to the waiting area.
-However…
-The link bridge is flooded,
so reinforcements can't make it through.
My valuable fountain pen is in there!
Get it back quickly!
-Please calm down.
-Leon!
A tactical unit is heading your way now.
However, due to the heavy rain,
it will take them about an hour to arrive.
That long?
What about Chief Hearing Officer Fukazawa?
He's at the main Immigration Bureau
and can't reach you.
Neither can we.
Until reinforcements arrive,
the remaining personnel must hold out.
Understood.
One hour.
So this place will be
an isolated island until then?
‎GATE24-SECONDARY ROOM
Don't answer that! Decline it!
Okay, okay.
Stop yelling at every little thing.
-Are you all right, Luca?
-Hey, move away!
-Stop cuddling up.
-What's the problem?
Hey, hey! Don't move.
May I clean up the luggage?
We should take care of the belongings.
Hey…
-Mori…
-Hayami.
It will take one hour
for the tactical unit to arrive.
Please hold out until then.
Hey, you!
Gunji. You're Gunji, aren't you?
Would you please talk to us?
We are not your enemies.
Our top priority is for everyone
to get out of here safely.
I hear you're a former coworker
of Tsuzuki.
Five years ago,
we started a company together.
But as soon as it got on track,
she kicked me out,
claiming "differences in direction".
-So you're doing this out of revenge?
-No!
Someone from the old company
reached out to me.
They said the CEO was recently obsessing
over a young foreigner.
-You mean me?
-That's right.
When did you start seeing this guy?
A year ago, when she came
to Unitia on business.
I suddenly felt unwell,
and Luca, who happened to be
passing by, took care of me.
A fateful meeting, you could call it.
What fate?
A young, handsome doctor
who just happened to be passing by?
Who's madly in love with you?
-How could anything be that convenient?
-It actually happened.
What?
-Are you jealous?
-No, I am not.
Let me tell you clearly.
This guy is a marriage fraudster!
A marriage fraudster?
That's the only explanation.
What he's after is money.
That and status to live in Japan.
What are you talking about?
Things like that happen, right?
Well, yes. There are cases
where foreign nationals
attempt to illegally obtain residency
through fake marriages.
-See?
-However,
marriage does not automatically
guarantee permission to live in Japan.
The actual reality of the marriage
and the couple's lives
are strictly examined.
Then
perform that examination
right now, right here!
Pardon?
Expose the fact that this guy
is deceiving Toko.
Until that's made clear,
no one leaves this room!
Examining…
love?
Luca is a scammer?
And we have to examine it here?
-The police, the police!
-Is it the tactical unit?
They're here already?
There, there, there!
Ah, finally made it.
-Iuchi?
-What? Yes.
Huh? Where's the tactical unit?
Not here yet. Only the two of us
were able to move ahead.
Sorry, but we aren't here as your backup.
-What?
-We were in the airport
investigating a separate matter.
We got a tip-off.
There's a possibility a marriage fraudster
is on this final flight.
Mori, what are you doing?
Inspecting.
Um, immigration is not a marriage agency,
nor can we evaluate human affection.
Just investigate him! He's a scammer!
Fine!
-If he insists, why not investigate?
-Um, like I said…
You saw it earlier, didn't you?
Luca's proposal.
That right there is proof of love.
Proof of love.
Toko, let me tell you this again.
-Will you--
-Don't do it now!
Um…
Excuse me.
That blue stone…
It's a sapphire.
I thought it'd look good on her.
May I take a look at it?
What are you doing?
I can see a few tiny air bubbles
inside the stone.
Air bubbles?
Natural sapphires contain inclusions.
However, having multiple
air bubbles like this
is a characteristic
commonly seen in glass.
Then that stone is…
I cannot say for certain,
but it may be a piece of glass,
made to imitate a sapphire.
A fake?
Is it this guy?
See?
He tried to trick you with a cheap ring!
It hasn't been proven fake yet.
Besides, the price doesn't matter.
As long as his feelings
are genuine, that's enough.
Um…
Actually, there is
one more thing that concerns me.
-One more thing?
-Yes.
Earlier, the woman at the adjacent booth
was wearing a similar ring.
-The woman next to us too?
-Yes.
Were you aware of this?
I don't know. Maybe it's a coincidence.
That couple too?
True, it is a similar ring.
Now that you mention it, I saw something.
During the proposal earlier.
Luca and Leon?
Those two might know each other.
Iuchi.
Could you folks
help us out a bit?
Leon.
A conversation?
Since the inspection
was interrupted earlier,
-we'd like to continue.
-Is there still something else?
You mentioned you're engaged.
When and how did you meet?
It was fate.
Just like how stones draw people in,
we were drawn to each other--
A dating app.
What?
There's an app for celebrities.
We messaged for about a week
and instantly hit it off.
Right?
-A dating app?
-That's right.
When did you actually meet in person?
-It's as if in a past life we knew--
-Three days ago.
-What?
I went all the way to Unitia,
and that was our first meeting.
The moment we met, we both knew
we were the one for each other.
Time doesn't matter in love.
They met through an app
and got engaged right away.
There is being efficient,
and then there is this.
Both of them got engaged
to Japanese corporate executives
and gave them similar rings.
These two…
might be in cahoots.
METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
Is the tactical unit still not there?
Pacing around
won't make them arrive any faster.
How can you remain so calm?
It's a hostage situation!
A hostage situation!
And it's terrible weather outside.
Everything is completely unexpected.
Crises always exceed expectations.
Only our ground staff can deal with it.
All we can do is trust them.
Hayami, Mori.
This is Iuchi from Tokyo Police.
The guy named Luca there
and that guy Leon over here
might belong to the same
marriage fraud ring.
We checked Leon Araki,
but found no record
of his activity as a gem appraiser.
I'm just providing you with info.
The tactical unit arrives in 20 minutes.
Do not provoke the suspect
under any circumstances.
Hey. What are you doing?
Take it off.
You too, off!
That was close.
Audio is still being picked up.
But they can't contact us now.
From here on, it depends on those two.
-Um…
-What is it?
Um, Luca, you came to Japan
to study abroad, right?
-Yes.
-That's right.
Obtaining a medical license
in Japan is Luca's dream.
But for a student about to study
abroad long-term,
I don't see any study material here.
What?
Not a single medical textbook
or reference book.
I was planning to get them in Japan.
Is that so?
Regarding your study abroad,
I have a question as well.
Luca, have you already paid
the tuition for your school?
Of course he has. Right?
The documents earlier contained neither
a payment confirmation nor a receipt.
Even an email would be enough.
Do you have anything?
Luca?
If we cannot confirm
the reality of your studies,
we cannot permit entry into the country.
Huh? He can't enter Japan?
That's great news.
You paid it, right?
Luca, check your account.
-Right now?
-Yes.
-Here?
-Hey.
-Just give it to me.
Here, open it.
21,136 YEN
It's gone.
Why isn't it here?
I'm sure I transferred it here!
Twenty million yen!
T-Twenty million?
That's a massive amount.
Tsuzuki, you gave that much to Luca?
What's wrong with that?
Luca had student loan debt back home
and was about to give up
on becoming a doctor.
That's why I decided to support
his tuition and living expenses.
That's a typical textbook scam.
I'm paying for everything.
-What?
His travel expenses,
living costs in Japan,
all of it is paid by me. Right?
It's just a temporary advance.
I happened to tie up my funds
for a major purchase recently.
I hope your work goes smoothly.
Aoi, thank you.
In this case, it's also the woman paying.
These two men are looking
more and more similar.
Hey, Luca.
Where did my money go?
Did you splurge it all away or something?
Be honest.
Give me that.
Akane? Who's that?
Is she your lover in Japan?
Was she the real reason you came to Japan?
How much longer
are you planning to trick Toko?
-Gunji…
-Um…
I have one request.
I want to inspect
the ingredients of those pills.
The pills?
Yes. The ones Tsuzuki was taking.
I've been wondering the whole time
whether they're really just supplements.
How are you going to inspect them?
Entered the underground passage.
ETA about ten minutes.
Roger that. We've got an entry plan.
This is Matsuyama.
I'm the only one standing
in front of the door.
I am going to open the door now.
Don't try anything funny.
I won't.
Slowly, okay?
Okay.
When am I getting my fountain pen back?
-Leon, please calm down.
-The police are about to come in, right?
-Wait!
-What if it gets scratched?
Police?
Mori.
My goodness.
This is bad.
Why is the police coming?!
So you were using this
to snitch to them after all!
-No…
-Don't lie to me, you bastard!
You were pretending to cooperate
just to buy time!
-That's not true. I'm--
-Shut up!
I can't trust any of you anymore!
-Gunji!
-It isn't over yet!
It isn't over?
T-The inspection.
There is still a place we haven't checked.
Mori.
Please look.
-Look in this bag.
-What's that?
May I open it?
-Wait--
-Don't move!
Open it.
Pardon me.
-"Dear Luca"?
-Give it back!
"To my beloved Luca.
If anything should happen to me,
I bequeath my corporate shares
and all my assets to you,
Luca Bennett."
What is this?
Is it a will?
No, there's no date,
so it doesn't seem to be formal.
I was just organizing my feelings
before consulting a lawyer.
Feelings?
Forget about 20 million.
You intended to give
this guy all your assets?
You knew that?
When I wrote this, that was my intention.
I wanted to support Luca's dream
and thought of it as proof of love.
But now I don't know anymore.
You didn't pay the tuition.
You won't say where
the 20 million went either.
Nor the real reason you came to Japan.
Hey.
What is the meaning of this, Luca?
The test results
for the medicine just came back.
A component called
norglycemide was detected.
Norglycemide.
What's that?
It's certainly not an ingredient
in a beauty supplement.
It strongly affects the body's metabolism,
and if overdosed, carries a risk
of inducing a coma.
Worst case, it could be life-threatening.
Life-threatening?
You weren't just tricking Toko,
you were trying to kill her?
No, I would never--
If Toko dies, you get all her assets.
Then, with that Akane woman in Japan…
-Toko…
-Enough!
I was such a fool.
I blindly assumed it was fate.
TO MY BELOVED LUCA
I'm glad I found out…
before it came to this.
Um…
Why did you write
that will?
You said it was "proof of love",
but I don't understand love
very well,
so I wanted you to tell me.
I told you
I collapsed a year ago
in the Unitia Federation, right?
Yes. Luca happened to pass by
and helped you.
I found that out later.
The truth is,
my vision suddenly went dark,
and I lost consciousness right then.
What?
I recovered at first,
but after that,
I kept getting cold sweats,
my hands shook.
I got sick over and over.
Back then,
I seriously thought I might die.
But…
even after helping me,
Luca took care of me.
I wanted to thank him,
so I supported him in my own way.
The will was the same.
It felt like…
Luca gave me my life back.
Um, Tsuzuki.
Regarding those symptoms,
did you also experience
palpitations or intense hunger?
I did.
How did you know?
Those are symptoms of hypoglycemia.
The medicine earlier, norglycemide,
acts to raise blood sugar levels.
While dangerous for healthy individuals,
if your blood sugar drops too low,
it serves as medicine to prevent attacks.
Then this guy was trying to…
Rather than trying to kill you,
maybe he was trying to protect you.
Why did you stay silent about that?
Was there a circumstance
that kept you from speaking?
Tell me.
Toko.
You have a tumor
in your pancreas.
A tumor?
It has already spread to your liver.
It's too advanced to remove surgically.
Is it incurable?
I've tried to tell you many times,
but you said you didn't want to hear it
until things settled down at work.
Toko!
-Toko!
-Are you all right?
Luca.
Toko, can you hear me?
What are those candies?
It's glucose.
Chew them slowly.
Now, let's slow the breathing down.
Breathe out slowly. That's it.
You're okay.
She's calming down.
Let me call the hospital, just to be safe.
The hospital?
Does this "Akane"
refer to the hospital?
Huh?
This is Akane Medical Center.
This is Luca Bennett.
I'm calling again about Toko Tsuzuki.
Please put me through
to her doctor, Shidagama.
So that's what it was.
Then everything was for Toko's sake?
-Her blood pressure has dropped again.
-It appears so.
‎Currently applying first-aid
‎as quickly as I can.
Luca isn't a scammer at all.
He was caring for Toko the whole time.
Iuchi!
The tactical unit has arrived.
What's the situation?
Inside the secondary room,
one suspect, four hostages.
-Get into position.
-Yes, sir.
Could you hold off for a bit?
I am Iuchi
from the International Crime Division.
The situation inside has changed.
The suspect is starting to calm down.
Right now, Gate 24 staff
are risking their lives
to resolve things inside.
I understand. Thank you very much.
Luca.
What about the money I gave you?
It seems
all of it went toward
your medical expenses, Tsuzuki.
Medication, consultation requests
to the medical center,
preparations for tests and treatment.
Including future expenses,
he likely didn't spend
a single yen on himself.
One more thing.
Luca.
You got a job at Akane Medical Center,
didn't you?
What?
Helping foreign patients
and assisting with medical examinations.
Of course,
you will need to pass through Immigration
again, with the proper procedures.
Then,
for your living expenses in Japan,
you intend to earn them yourself?
Why?
Like I said before,
you've always been there for me.
Now I want to be there for you.
I don't want your inheritance.
You don't have to stay with me.
Please…
put your health first.
Toko.
I didn't notice a single thing.
I'm sorry.
This is Hayami.
Gunji has surrendered his weapon.
He has no intent to resist.
I am opening the door.
On your knees!
-Search him.
-Roger.
On the floor!
Nothing on him.
Apparently, the person who reported
a scammer on this flight was Gunji.
Gunji?
Thanks to that,
we were able to get this far.
Well, in reality,
-the actual scammer was someone else.
-Look!
This scratch!
What have you done?
We need to confiscate it as a weapon.
Do you realize how valuable this item is?
That fountain pen is not worth that much.
Excuse me.
Underneath the scratch,
another metal is visible.
This is not solid gold.
It's plated on the surface.
The decorative stone is also just glass.
Also, we heard from Luca.
Before coming here,
you sold him a ring, right?
You claimed it was a real sapphire.
We have a lot of questions to ask you.
Onodera.
Most likely, that ring as well.
I know.
I can tell it's a fake.
You knew?
I called myself a CEO,
but my company is small.
I'm the only employee.
What?
I want to hire people,
but things haven't gone well.
So, perhaps you dated Leon…
Not to find a marriage partner,
but an employee?
Aoi?
I knew you were full of lies.
But your smooth talking and nerve,
those at least were real.
Tell everything to the police
and make amends for what you've done.
And then,
if you intend to turn your life around…
come to me.
What's your answer?
Yes.
-Well then, right this way.
-Okay.
May we talk to you as well, Onodera?
Yes.
Tsuzuki.
Thank you for your help.
I will pay Luca's tuition immediately.
That will satisfy
the purpose of entry, right?
Toko.
‎Yes.
Thank you very much.
APPROVED BY IMMIGRATION
Good luck.
‎Thank you.
-Here you are.
-Thank you very much.
Welcome to Japan.
‎Thank you.
So this is love.
-I'm glad they resolved it safely.
-Yes.
Thanks to the brave people on the ground.
You really seem to trust Gate 24.
Yes. It's the team I built, after all.
Your team, huh?
I hope that trust is never betrayed.
Goodbye.
It's been a while, huh?
What's going on?
I have a favor to ask.
I want you to look for a spy.
What do you mean?
We received a report
that for the past two months,
there have been people involved
with terrorists and extremists
entering the country at a rapid scale.
Gate 24 has become
a shortcut for terrorists.
There's a spy in Gate 24?
I want you to look for that spy.
I'm counting on you.
Mori.
Oh my.
‎AT LAST, THE FINAL CHAPTER!
‎Inspection is temporarily halted
‎at the moment.
‎-I'm a doctor.
‎-Was it an accident,
‎-or on purpose?
‎-‎Someone among us
‎is in direct contact with a person
‎suspected of being a spy.
‎If there really is a spy at Gate 24…
‎-This is…
‎-Oh my.
Subtitle translation by: Maslin Friedman